skinvideo.com 2012-10-04

# Privacy Policy

##  SkinVideo Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting SkinVideo. Your privacy is important to us. This privacy policy explains the information we collect and what we use it for. What we collect and how we use it

SkinVideo may ask you to provide personally identifiable information, such as your name, contact information, and credit card number. In addition, we may ask you to provide your password, user identification number, and we may collect information regarding your internet protocol address and browser type. When a visitor provides such information to us, we use it to deliver requested goods, services or information, provide notices regarding goods or services you may purchase, verify your identity to use SkinVideo, and improve the functioning of the website. 

### Cookies

Cookies are small text files that are stored in your web browser. The use of cookies is now standard operating procedure for most web sites. While cookies generally do not permit us to personally identify you, we use them to help us improve the SkinVideo experience for you and other customers. If you do not wish to share cookie data with us, your web browser may offer you the option to block our cookies. Because SkinVideo was designed to use cookies, blocking them will reduce site functionality. 

### Disclosure

We may provide aggregate data regarding site usage to our third party partners. We will also disclose your personally identifiable information if we reasonably believe we are required to do so by law, regulation or other government authority or to prevent harm to yourself or others. In addition, we may transfer your personally identifiable information to a successor entity upon a merger, consolidation or other corporate reorganization in which SkinVideo participates or to a purchaser of all or substantially all of SkinVideo's assets. Such successor entity shall be bound by the terms and conditions of this privacy policy. 

### Harassment

If you harass or publish private information on our site about the models on our site (whether appearing in previously recorded videos or live chat rooms), your IP address may be provided to the model to assist in identifying you and ending the harassment. 

### Links to Third Party Sites

SkinVideo may be linked to other web sites on the Internet which are not under the control of or maintained by SkinVideo. Such links do not constitute an endorsement by SkinVideo of those other web sites, the content displayed therein, or the persons or entities associated therewith. You acknowledge that SkinVideo is providing these links to you only as a convenience, and you agree that SkinVideo is not responsible for the content of such sites. Your use of these other linked web sites is subject to the respective terms of use and privacy policies located on the linked sites. 

### Security

SkinVideo employs procedural and technological measures, consistent with the demands of customer service. Such measures are reasonably designed to protect your personally identifiable information from loss, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. Where practical, SkinVideo uses encryption, password protection, firewalls, internal restrictions and other security measures to help prevent unauthorized access to your personally identifiable information. 

### Updating Your Information

If you wish to update your personally identifiable information please contact SkinVideo at the address or e-mail address provided below. 

### Policy Changes

SkinVideo reserves the right to change this privacy policy, and will post any revisions on its website located at www.skinvideo.com. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Your continued use of this web site will be subject to the then-current privacy policy. 

If you have questions or comments regarding SkinVideo's privacy practices you can contact us at: SVG Technology, Inc., 548 Market Street #90461, San Francisco, CA 94104 or admin@skinvideo.com. We will be sure to address your concerns.
